Guide to the Ellington Field research collection, 1917-2009 MS 547
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Ellington Field research collection
1917-2009
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Morrow, Kathryn Black
MS 547
5.5 Linear Feet (11 boxes)
This collection contains ten boxes of material related to the history and operation of Ellington Field, also known as Ellington Air Force Base, near Houston, Texas. The majority of the records date from 1917-2007, and include historical research materials, photographs, books, microfilm, postcards, and memorabilia. The foundation of the collection was material assembled by historian Kathryn Black Morrow for the publication of a history of Ellington Field.
Historical Sketch
Ellington Field was officially opened November 27, 1917, as the United States' largest pilot and navigator training base, and the nation's first aerial bombing school. By the end of World War I, Ellington Field had grown to the size of a small city which housed 20,000 men and 250 aircraft. Like most bases, it was closed after World War I, but unlike most other military installations, it was reopened and saw at least partial use until World War II, when it was rebuilt as one of ten strategic defense bases in the United States. It was the only strategic defense base on the Gulf Coast. The location of the field was, and still is, crucial to the defense of the Houston Ship Channel, the ports of Galveston and Houston and one of the United States' largest oil refining centers. In 2005, the field was once again expanded to become a Joint Reserves base, to house the combined military forces Reserve Units. In 2005, the U.S. Department of Defense recommended retiring Ellington Field's 147th Fighter Wing F-16 Falcon fighter jets. The aircraft were replaced with MQ-1 Predator unmanned drones and the unit was redesignated as the 147th Reconnaissance Wing. The ANG 272nd Engineering Installation Squadron, was also relocated to Ellington Field. From 1976 to 2007, Ellington Field was partially owned and managed by the Houston Airport System, and the base was also home to the Texas State Guard, NASA's Johnson Space Center, a U.S. Coast Guard Search and Rescue unit, and other aviation related businesses.
Kathryn Black Morrow (1948- ) assembled this collection during her research for a master's thesis, which she completed at the University of Houston, Clear Lake campus, in 2003. She expanded her thesis research and published a history of Ellington Field called Defender of America's Gulf Coast, A History of Ellington Field, Texas 1917-2007, in 2007. Ms. Morrow was born in Houston Texas, and works as a researcher, writer of Texas history, and archivist. Her other books include "Guide to the Texas Slave Trade Series, 1818-1886, The 79th Aviation Squadron, Ellington Field, Texas, in World War II, Southeast Texas Colored Voter Registrations, 1867-1869," and "Meant to Fly; The Memoirs of Captain A.J. High, Pilot for Trans-Texas Airways."
Scope and Contents
The Ellington Field research collection relates to the history of Ellington Field (later designated Ellington Air Force Base) and the development of military aviation from World War I through to the Space Age. Subjects include the history of the airfield and some of the units that served there, women in the military at Ellington Field, African Americans in the military, NASA, Johnson Space Center, the Air National Guard, Texas National Gaurd, and the Houston Airport System. Photographs date from 1917- 2007, diaries, postcards and memorabilia date from World War I and World War II. Two rolls of microfilm from the Air Force History and Research Agency ( AFHRA) contain the base records and reports from 1940-1945. Documentation includes Morrow's research notes and copies of primary sources such as crash investigation reports, Houston Aiport System records, leases, press releases and newspaper clippings. Books include diaries, memoirs, unit histories, and military histories. Recorded and live interviews date from 1967-2007.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research. Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Accruals
Future additions may be expected for this material.
Acquisition Information
This collection was donated by Kathryn Black Morrow May 4, 2009.
Index Terms
Subjects
African Americans; World War (1939-1945); Cold War; Texas Red River Campaign, March-May 1864; 147th Fighter Interceptor Group, Ellington Field, Texas; African Americans in the military; Military Aviation, 20th Century; Race discrimination; Coast Guard; World War (1914-1918); WAC(Women's Army Corps); Women and the military; Women; Military
Document Types
corrrespondence; memorabilia; microfilms; clippings (information artifacts); pamphlets; photographs; audiotapes; books
Subjects (Persons)
Morrow, Kathryn Black; Bush, George W. (George Walker); Wells, Stephanie, Lt. Col.; Stepchinski, Aloysius, Colonel; Sharp, George, Lt. Col.; Salton Clark, Laurel; Reid, Walter H., Col.; Radcliffe, Vaughan; Parker, William; McLeaish, John; McCool, William; Lang, Dave; Kinzler, Jack; Jernigan, Tamara; Jemison, Mae; Ivins, Marsha; Hjornevik, Wesley; Grimm, Dean; Helms, Susan; Godwin, Linda; Goforth, Art, Colonel; Chawla, Kalpana; Edmonds, Eugene; Byerly, Kirk, Capt.; Byrnes, Martin; Brown, David; Anderson, Michael; Aldridge, Roy; Algranti, Joe
- Series I: Ellington Field research materials, 1917-2009
  - Written histories, 1950-1963. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Articles, evolution of the Air Force, 1914-2002. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Articles, general aviation and local history, 1917-2001. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - History, 111th Fighter Squadron, 1917-2007. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - History, 147th Fighter Interceptor Group, 1990-2007. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - History, 158th Aircraft Control and Warning Group, 1951-2002. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - History, 340th Navigation Training Squadron, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - History, 2516th AAF Base Unit, Eagle Pass, Texas, 1945. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - History, 446th Tactical Airlift Wing, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Histories, 3605th Aircraft Observer Training Unit, 1950-1955. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Articles, Johnson Space Center, "Space News Roundup", 1963-1991. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Johnson Space Center Economic Impact Studies, 1967,1980. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Johnson Space Center History Collection information, 2003. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Oral history interviews 1943, 1967,1968, 2004. Note: MSC/JSC Interviewees (1967,1968) were Dave Lang, Joe Algranti, Dean Grimm,Wesley Hjornevik, John McLeaish, Roy Aldridge,Martin Byrnes, Eugene Edmonds, Capt. Kirk Byerly, Jack Kinzler, William Parker. NASA biographies were of Marsha Ivins, Tamara Jernigan,Linda Godwin, Mae Jemison,Susan Helms,Kalpana Chawla, William McCool, David Brown, Michael Anderson, and Laurel Salton Clark. Live interviews (2004) by Kathryn Black Morrow were Lt. Col. George Sharp, Vaughan Radcliffe, Col. Art Goforth. Ellington Field World War II interviews (1943) were Lt. Col. James H. von Pein, Mrs. Walter H. Reid, T/Sgt. Robert G. Hahn, Mr. R.A. Laird, Mrs. Alexine G. Watts, Mr. Robert A. Wilkins, Col. Walter H. Reid (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Joint Use Agreements, GSA, NASA, Air Force, 1978-1979, 1981-1983. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Closing of Ellington as an active duty base, 1975-1976. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - History, Project Gemini, book excerpt, 2002. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Texas Military Forces, Economic Impact, 1996, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Ellington Field Master Plan Studies, 1987,2002. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Houston Airport System Economic Impact Study, 1998. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Press releases, memoranda, articles, 1967,2007. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Wings Over Houston Souvenir programs, 2002, 2009. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Articles, air races, 1916-1920. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Certificate copies, 1919,1942. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Newsclippings, 1917-1920. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Newsclippings, 1921-1925. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Newsclippings, 1940-1945. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Newsclippings, 1946-1949. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Newsclippings, 1950-1954. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Newsclippings, 1955-1959. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Newsclippings, 1960-1969. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Newsclippings, 1970-1979. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Newsclippings, 1980-1985. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Newsclippings, 1986-1889. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Newsclippings, 1990-1995. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Newsclippings, 1996-2000. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Newsclippings, 2001-2004. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Newsclippings, 2004-2007. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Cassette tape, TDK 90 minute, KUHF 88.7 FM Radio Station, Interviewer, Paul Pendergraft. Interview 1., Col. Steve Jones, Vice Flight Commander,147th Fighter Interceptor Group, Texas Air National Guard, Ellington Field,October 9, 2001, Interview 2. Col. Bob Luna, Military Public Affairs Officer, Texas National Guard, Ellington Field, October 14, 2001. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - AFHRA Microfilm reel, B2175, Ellington Field historical records, 1940-1946. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - AFHRA Microfilm reel, B2176, Ellington Field historical records, 1944-1946. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Ellington Field Joint Reserve Base promotional buttons, undated. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Civil Air Patrol manuals, history, 1992- 1994. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Texas National Guard newsclippings, 1968-1975. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - National Guard magazine, 50th anniversary issue, June 1994. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Adjutant General's Office overview, Texas National Guard, Texas State Guard histories, undated. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Military Equal Opportunity Climate survey, c. 1991. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Historical records copies, Air Force History and Research Agency (AFHRA) microfilm reel B2175, items 7, 8, 12, 15., 1940-1944. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Historical records copies, Air Force History and Research Agency (AFHRA) microfilm reel B2176, items 3, 4, 6., 1944-1945. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Historical records copies, Air Force History and Research Agency (AFHRA) microfilm reel B2175, item 6., 1944. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Articles, newsclippings, 2002-2007. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Programs, memorabilia, 1917-2007. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, 1914-2007. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Postcards, World War I, World War II, 1917-1945. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Book, Ellington 1918 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Letters home from Ellington Field; Osgood, Merriman, 1943, 1994. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Letters home from Ellington Field, Cadet Ira McNair diary, 1 of 2, 1918. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Letters home from Ellington Filed, Cadet Ira McNair diary, 2 of 2, 1918. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - "Searching the Skies; The Legacy of the United Satate's Defense Radar Program", c. 1985-1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - "Reach for the Skies" promotional brochure, Clear Lake Economic Development Foundation, 1987- 1991. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Booklet, " A Camera Trip Through Ellington Field", c. 1943. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Book, Ellington Field Class 43-D, 1943. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Book, Ellington Field Class 43K, 1943. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Book, "The Astro-Dome," Ellington Field Class 44-3, 1944. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Book, "No Mindus de Murkus," A History of the Air National Guard Jet Instrument School, Ellington Field, 1957-1961. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - "Aviation Weekly' magazine, May 27, 1968. Note: Article on Lunar Landing vehicle (LLV) crash involving Col. Neil Armstrong on page 55. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - "Tailspin" newspaper November 19, 1943. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - "Texas, the Defense Community," Texas Military Preparedness Commission Annual Report 2004-2005. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - "Texas Military History Quarterly," Note: Article Military Aviation in Texas, 1917-1919 includes information on the establishment of Ellington Field on pages 8,9. The article, " Texas Forces in the Red River Campaign, March-May 1864, pages 15-22 includes a map of the campaign in an envelope at the back of the magazine..., Spring, 1963. (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Series II: Personnel Photographs
  - Abbey, George W.S. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Abbott, Ross M. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Adams, Claude B., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Adams, Edwin W., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Adams, Thomas C., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Adamson, Thomas W. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Adger, John H. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Adkins, John W. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Ahrens, Clarence R. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Akin, Frank A. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Akin, Robert G. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Albels, Ernest E. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Alford, R.L. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Allbright, Joe E. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Allen, Gale H. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Allen, Julius C. (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Allen, Michael E. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Allen, Michael H. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Allen, Robert G. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Allen, Samuel J. (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Anderson, Bobbie D. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Anderson, Darryl K. (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Anderson, Kenneth D. (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Anglin, Jerry P. (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Antill, Gene C., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Archer, Donald L. (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Armstrong, Nobel B., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Arnold, Glenn T. (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Arnold, Jerry N. (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Arnold, Willie R. (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Artiaga, Pete (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Ash, Jimmie C. (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Atkins, Thomas A. (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Atwill, James H. (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Ault, Donald E. (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Avenell, Paul R. (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Aycock, Hollis E. (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Baer, Robert G. (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Bailey, Eldridge B. (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Baker, Earl J. (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Baker, Franklin R. (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Baker, James A. (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Baker, Robert A. (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Baker, Vernon E., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Baker, William J., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Baldwin, William D. (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Ballard, Hoyt B. (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Banzer, Franz A., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Barfield, Billy J. (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Bariteau, Albert A. (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Barko, Andrew J. (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Barmore, Gaston C., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Barnell, David K. (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Barnes, Bernard E. (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Barnes, Joseph E. (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Barnes, Lewis W., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Barnett, Clyde R. (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Barnett, Derrell L. (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Barnett, Donald M. (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Barnhart, Donald D. (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Barrera, George T. (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Barrera, Narciso (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Barrett, Kenneth H. (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Barstow, William F. (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Bartels, Victor J. (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Bartle, Thomas F. (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Barton, Cecil L. (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Bartula, Raymond A. (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Bascom, Clarence C., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Bass, James D. (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Bath, James R. (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Bauerkemper, Gary R. (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Baugh, William F., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Beach, James R. (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Beall, H.H. (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Beall, James L. (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Beard, Oliver C., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Beck, Billy B. (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Becker, Robert L. (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Befeld, Herman A.. (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Belcher, Edgar M. (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Bennett, Jimmy L. (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Bensen, Jan A. (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Benton, Donald A. (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Bernshausen, Clarence (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Berryman, Bernard C. (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Bertelson, Roger A. (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Bertram, Emil O. (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Best, L.C. (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Bilsky, James C. (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Bishop, James E., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Blanco, Bobby G. (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Blankenship, Charles V., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Blankenship, Earl (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Blankenship, Randle L., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Bleil, Bert E. (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Blevins, William V. (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Blissard, Robert J. (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Block, James A. (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Bock, Edward S., III (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Bolin, Rex E. (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Bond, William H. (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Bonner, Jerry W. (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Bookout, Ronald L. (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Boothe, Walter T. (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Booton, Richard L. (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Bordelon, Darvin A. (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Borden, Richard B. (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Bosworth, Ted L. (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Bowen, James W. (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Bowman, James M. (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Boxx, Eldon L. (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Brady, James P. (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Brant, Charles E. (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Brasfield, Lee L. (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Bravenec, Robert R. (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Brazell, Ernest C. (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Brent, John B. (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Briggs, William (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Bright, David E. (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Briscoe, James R. (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - Britt, George W., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Brock, James E. (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Broussard, Eloie C., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Brown, James C. (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Brown, Jimmie D. (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - Broyles, Walter S. (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Bruder, Harry E. (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Bruemmer, Robert E. (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - Bryan, James D., III (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - Bryant, James M. (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Buchanan, Carroll L. (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - Buchanan, Ronald J. (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - Burroughs, James C. (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - Busch, Robert D. (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - Butcher, William L., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - Butler, Albert D., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - Butler, Marshall W., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - Buxton, Charles W. (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - Caddell, Leon J., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - Caffey, Clarence R. (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Caldwell, Alan B. (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - Caldwell, Charlie (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Calvert, Kenneth E. (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - Campbell, Walter D. (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Canady, James P. (Box 7, Folder 146)
  - Caplovitz, Nathan (Box 7, Folder 147)
  - Carbone, Charles M. (Box 7, Folder 148)
  - Carby, Wayne K. (Box 7, Folder 149)
  - Carpenter, Gerald D. (Box 7, Folder 150)
  - Carr, Marion A. (Box 7, Folder 151)
  - Carr, Rex B. (Box 7, Folder 152)
  - Carrillo, Albert A. (Box 7, Folder 153)
  - Carroll, David V. (Box 7, Folder 154)
  - Carroll, Gayle G. (Box 7, Folder 155)
  - Carroll, James R. (Box 7, Folder 156)
  - Carter, James B. (Box 7, Folder 157)
  - Carter, James R. (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Carter, Robert C. (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Casey, Kenneth R. (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Cash, Joseph A. (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Castillo, Jose G. (Box 7, Folder 162)
  - Castro, Guadalupe, Jr. (Box 7, Folder 163)
  - Cauley, James M. (Box 7, Folder 164)
  - Chadwick, James L. (Box 7, Folder 165)
  - Challton, Robert L. (Box 7, Folder 166)
  - Chamberlain, Robert E. (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - Chambers, Raymond W., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Chaney, Clair V. (Box 7, Folder 169)
  - Chapman, William P., III (Box 7, Folder 170)
  - Charlton, Robert R. (Box 7, Folder 171)
  - Chaudier, James B. (Box 7, Folder 172)
  - Cheatham, Robert D. (Box 7, Folder 173)
  - Chilek, Charlie F. (Box 7, Folder 174)
  - Chilek, Davie S. (Box 7, Folder 175)
  - Christa, David L. (Box 7, Folder 176)
  - Christmas, Carl K. (Box 7, Folder 177)
  - Clark, James W. (Box 7, Folder 178)
  - Clay, Kenneth B. (Box 7, Folder 179)
  - Coker, Raymond L. (Box 7, Folder 180)
  - Cole, James E. (Box 7, Folder 181)
  - Cole, Raymond E. (Box 7, Folder 182)
  - Coleman, William R. (Box 7, Folder 183)
  - Conner, Floyd O. (Box 7, Folder 184)
  - Conrad, Ronald O. (Box 7, Folder 185)
  - Contreras, Herman A. (Box 7, Folder 186)
  - Cook, Alton H., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 187)
  - Cook, Charles H. (Box 7, Folder 188)
  - Cook, John C. (Box 7, Folder 189)
  - Cooke, Gary L. (Box 7, Folder 190)
  - Cooper, Coral L. (Box 7, Folder 191)
  - Cooper, John H., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 192)
  - Cortez, Ricardo, Sr. (Box 7, Folder 193)
  - Coskey, Johnny A. (Box 7, Folder 194)
  - Coslett, Walter R. (Box 7, Folder 195)
  - Cotrone, Joseph C. (Box 7, Folder 196)
  - Counce, Jackie W. (Box 7, Folder 197)
  - Coupland, Robert D. (Box 7, Folder 198)
  - Cox, James M. (Box 7, Folder 199)
  - Crain, James T. (Box 7, Folder 200)
  - Craven, Joseph L. (Box 7, Folder 201)
  - Croes, Mirto D. (Box 7, Folder 202)
  - Croes, Sixto R. (Box 7, Folder 203)
  - Cromwell, Henry A., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 204)
  - Crone, Roy D. (Box 7, Folder 205)
  - Crump, Major James T. (Box 7, Folder 206)
  - Crump, Ray A. (Box 7, Folder 207)
  - Cuevas, Roy R. (Box 7, Folder 208)
  - Culbreth, Alfred B. (Box 7, Folder 209)
  - Cummings, Harry J. (Box 7, Folder 210)
  - Cummings, Lawrence C. (Box 7, Folder 211)
  - Cunningham, Ronald E. (Box 7, Folder 212)
  - Currier, Charles D. (Box 7, Folder 213)
  - Cuthbertson, Floyd E. (Box 7, Folder 214)
  - Czekanski, Ronald W. (Box 7, Folder 215)
  - Dabney, William R. (Box 7, Folder 216)
  - Daigle, Wayne D. (Box 7, Folder 217)
  - Darling, William D. (Box 7, Folder 218)
  - Daugherty, John A., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 219)
  - Davis, Arthur R. (Box 7, Folder 220)
  - Davis, Bobby A. (Box 7, Folder 221)
  - Davis, Carl F. (Box 7, Folder 222)
  - Davis, Carl F. (Box 7, Folder 223)
  - Davis, James A. (Box 7, Folder 224)
  - Davis, Jon M. (Box 7, Folder 225)
  - Davis, Lyn D. (Box 7, Folder 226)
  - Davis, P.E. (Box 7, Folder 227)
  - Davis, Ralph D. (Box 7, Folder 228)
  - Davis, Robert G. (Box 7, Folder 229)
  - Deanovich, Michael G. (Box 7, Folder 230)
  - Dehart, Richard W. (Box 7, Folder 231)
  - Dehay, Hedwig H. (Box 7, Folder 232)
  - Desazo, Robert T. (Box 7, Folder 233)
  - Dever, James P. (Box 7, Folder 234)
  - Deviney, Howard L., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 235)
  - Dewees, Olen E., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 236)
  - Dicamillo, Lawrence R. (Box 7, Folder 237)
  - Dicker, Charles, A., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 238)
  - Dickson, Thomas E., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 239)
  - Dietrich, Frank B. (Box 7, Folder 240)
  - Dimicelli, Joseph A. (Box 7, Folder 241)
  - Dimler, Dale R. (Box 7, Folder 242)
  - Divin, Albert J. (Box 7, Folder 243)
  - Dobbins, James R. (Box 7, Folder 244)
  - Doehring, Billy J. (Box 7, Folder 245)
  - Dombrowski, Henry T. (Box 7, Folder 246)
  - Donaldson, John W. (Box 7, Folder 247)
  - Doran, Harold G.. (Box 7, Folder 248)
  - Dougherty, James A. (Box 7, Folder 249)
  - Douglas, Donald C. (Box 7, Folder 250)
  - Douglas, Garth D. (Box 7, Folder 251)
  - Dowell, Aubrey C. (Box 7, Folder 252)
  - Dowler, Earl R. (Box 7, Folder 253)
  - Dowling, Alfred P., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 254)
  - Downes, Robert W. (Box 7, Folder 255)
  - Dudley, Donald G. (Box 7, Folder 256)
  - Dudley, Ronald D. (Box 7, Folder 257)
  - Due, Grady D. (Box 7, Folder 258)
  - Dukeminier, Randell A. (Box 7, Folder 259)
  - Dumkay, William H. (Box 7, Folder 260)
  - Dunavent, Dale E. (Box 7, Folder 261)
  - Dunkin, Lawrence G. (Box 7, Folder 262)
  - Dunn, Robert E. (Box 7, Folder 263)
  - Dunne, Thomas Y. (Box 7, Folder 264)
  - Durant, Cecil J. (Box 7, Folder 265)
  - Dyer, Michael H. (Box 7, Folder 266)
  - Dyer, Walter C., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 267)
  - Dynis, Dale N. (Box 7, Folder 268)
  - Earle, James K. (Box 7, Folder 269)
  - Ebersole, Frank E. (Box 7, Folder 270)
  - Eckert, Charles M. (Box 7, Folder 271)
  - Eddings, Selman D., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 272)
  - Edwards, Howard H., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 273)
  - Elam, Robert O. (Box 7, Folder 274)
  - Ellard, Charles J. (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - Ellis, Allen A. (Box 7, Folder 276)
  - Erickson, Eric W., Jr. (Box 7, Folder 277)
  - Escamilla, Johnny M. (Box 7, Folder 278)
  - Eubanks, Richard L. (Box 7, Folder 279)
  - Everhard, Clay (Box 7, Folder 280)
  - Ewing, Lawrence C. (Box 7, Folder 281)